soft-go.com 2008-06-08

# Soft-Go.Com - Privacy Policy

|  Categories   
---  
Antivirus  
Compression tools  
CD-DVD Tools  
Office tools  
Programming  
Authoring tools  
File managers  
Desktop Enhancements  
Internet  
Network Tools  
Multimedia  
System  
Security  
Windows Widgets  
Science-CAD  
Misc Categories  
Weekly Top 10  
---  
1. | Samsung PC Studio  
2. | Raxso Enterprise  
3. | Raxso Drive Magic  
4. | Raxso Columbus  
5. | Quick Slide Show  
6. | AllMedia Grabber  
7. | Internet Download Manager  
8. | Global Downloader  
9. | LG Phone Manager  
10. | Clean MemXP  
  
---  
|  Privacy Policy:  
---  
Soft-Go® recognize the importance of protecting the privacy of all information provided by users of our web site, recipients of our e-mail newsletters and all other customers of our products and services. We created this policy with a fundamental respect for our customer's right to privacy and to guide our relationships with our customers. 

**E-mail Newsletters**  
If users wish to subscribe to our e-mail newsletters, we ask for email address. Recipients of our newsletters can unsubscribe using the instructions listed at the end of the e-mail newsletter. We do not share this information with third parties.

**Applications submissions**  
If developers wish to submit applications in order to be listed on our Web site, we ask for email address. The email address will be used to communicate with software developers. We do not share this information with third parties.

**Links**  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we Soft-Go.Com, are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other sites.   
We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.  
  
Disclaimer:  
  
Soft-Go.Com accepts no responsibility for the software you are downloading. Same policy apply to information provided about software product(s). Even if Soft-Go.Com try to verify every application listed on Web site for viruses, spyware, adware, trojans, we can't guarantee that they are 100% clean.  
Soft-Go.Com is not responsible for any damage, loss caused due to use of the contents on this website.   
| Business News  
---  
Dow falls 394.64 points on jobless rate, record oil (Reuters) 

[](http://us.rd.yahoo.com/dailynews/rss/business/*http://news.yahoo.com/s/nm/20080607/bs_nm/markets_stocks_dc)Reuters - Stocks plunged on Friday, marking the Dow's worst day in 15 months, after the government said the May unemployment rate jumped the most in 22 years and oil prices shot to another record, renewing fears that the U.S. economy faces 1970s-style stagflation.

Oil zooms nearly 9 percent higher to record $139 (Reuters) 

[](http://us.rd.yahoo.com/dailynews/rss/business/*http://news.yahoo.com/s/nm/20080607/bs_nm/markets_oil_dc)Reuters - Oil jumped nearly 9 percent to a record $139 a barrel on Friday, extending a two-day rally to more than $16 as the slumping U.S. dollar and mounting tensions between Israel and Iran attracted a stampede of buyers.

Singapore's Unisteel accepts $575 mln KKR bid (Reuters)   
Reuters - Singapore disc drive component maker Unisteel on Saturday said it has agreed to be bought by Kohlberg Kravis Roberts & Co. for $575 million.   
Agility could sign $2.5 billion U.S. army deal: report (Reuters)   
Reuters - Kuwait's Agility , the Gulf's biggest logistics provider by market value, is set to sign a $2.5 billion deal with the U.S. army in July, a newspaper reported on Sunday.   
Jobless rate leaps to 3-1/2 year high in May (Reuters) 

[](http://us.rd.yahoo.com/dailynews/rss/business/*http://news.yahoo.com/s/nm/20080606/bs_nm/usa_economy_jobs2_dc)Reuters - The U.S. unemployment rate surged to 5.5 percent in May, its highest in more than 3-1/2 years, as the barely growing economy lost jobs for the fifth straight month.

Delta unrest casts shadow on Nigeria and world economy (AFP) 

[](http://us.rd.yahoo.com/dailynews/rss/business/*http://news.yahoo.com/s/afp/20080608/bs_afp/nigeriaoilunrest)AFP - Unrest in the Niger Delta is becoming a major problem for the Nigerian government but its importance as an oil producer is also helping extend its shadow over the world economy.

Software News  
---  
Ending the Hardware/Software Rat Race (PC World)   
PC World - Could Microsoft's decision to extend the sales deadline for Windows XP signal a major strategic shift?   
Apple's 3G IPhone Could Bow at Developer Event (PC World)   
PC World - Apple could announce the 3G iPhone and a new software development platform for the phone at next week's developer conference.   
Windows XP To Windows 7 A Risky Path, Microsoft Warns (TechWeb)   
TechWeb - [InformationWeek](http://us.rd.yahoo.com/dailynews/cmp/tc_cmp/storytext/208402585/27780621/SIG=1315rlgls/*http://www.informationweek.com/;jsessionid=QXQG4V1BHI2JOQSNDLQSKH0CJUNN2JVN?cid=feed-yahoo-news) \- Customers that don't deploy Windows Vista are missing out on proven benefits such as better security, productivity, search, mobility, and manageability, says a Microsoft executive.   
Leaked Report Details Secret Ad Software Trials in UK (PC World)   
PC World - A leaked internal report detailing the secret test of a targeted advertising system by BT could fuel further complaints about...   
IBM to release enterprise mashup tool (InfoWorld)   
InfoWorld - IBM is getting closer to releasing its mashup technology, with plans to deliver an enterprise-ready software product in the third quarter, and a free trial version hosted on the Web that customers can test out beforehand.   
Last call for Windows XP PCs is mid-June (InfoWorld)   
InfoWorld - It???s last call for consumers to buy PCs pre-loaded with Windows XP.   
---
